[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Are you really, as a party, any nearer to knowing who will be the nominee?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Could this all be over by April or is it more likely, given what's been going on state by state so far, that this will run all the way to the convention?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "DT", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "I tend to think it'll be over before it goes to the convention but I can't prove that arithmetically.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["April"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "From a betting point of view, where do you think this is all heading?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "It's hard to say because every time you have one piece of conventional wisdom it's right for about a week and then wrong the next week, and flips back to being right again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Or is there something else going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "I certainly hope it's not the Mormon thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "But what is your sense about the apparent atrocity unfurling there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Well, we have a government that seems to be, in effect, devouring its own people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "What should America be doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Yes, I wish I could say that some of our followers, you know, produced the magic solution.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "What is the answer to how America should deal with their game?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "WRB", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Well, what we're seeing happen over Syria is really a kind of new alignment.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Will journalists got to get into Syria, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "What do you think about the situation involving the media there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, I mean, it's really hard to galvanize the international community to care about a crisis when you don't have a lot of footage coming in over television screens.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "It's not how do we fix this broken horror story, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, I would say the thing to do is to keep us strong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "What do you think has gone wrong and what should he be doing now to fix it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Well, let me say this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "What do you think is the biggest misconception about Mitt Romney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "And you believe he can bring that kind of business skill to America incorporated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "You bet.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Created?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Let's discuss that after the break.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Was it fair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "I think it was quite good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "JJ", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Did he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "\"Good afternoon.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Brangelina"]}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "You mean my daughter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "I mean Brangelina.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Is it weird to see how famous she's become?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "OIGHT: Well, it's -- yes, it's a very unusual thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "It has been a rocky road, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Famously.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "What's the most sensible advice that you as a former Oscar winner can give her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Well, you know, I did the best I could to try to give her advice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Was that an unfair thing to infer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Well, I think that -- I think I'm a better person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 345, "question": "What have you learned about yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "This is turning into a Piers Morgan --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Do you find it uncomfortable talking about yourself like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Well, it's not important.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jon Voight"]}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I'm great, but I'm feeling a little uncomfortable because I was going to tell the same story that Jon Voight just told.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "You're quite an active little Tweeter, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "I do like to Tweet, my friend.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tweeter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Do you find it's like taking over your life slightly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "It is addictive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Where is your money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "I think Obama.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Do you think any of them, even if they do win the nomination race, could actually beat Barack Obama, especially if the economy goes on improving the way that it is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "I find it fascinating, Piers, that you are having me on the show to really talk seriously about politics.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "You're a Democrat, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Well, I'm -- yes, I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "You're married to a Democrat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "I'm married to somebody who is not a Republican or a Democrat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "He's not a Democrat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Well, he doesn't say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 573, "question": "What are you trying to get out of me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "I don't know, some lurid revelation that's going to --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Are you trying to get me divorced?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Why did you -- I love this book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "And why did you go for this cover?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Well, two excellent questions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Didn't you once get into a bathing suit with Henry Kissinger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Henry Kissinger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "Who sets you up on this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "I was at a party.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "Probably a tendency to get on desks and come raging towards you like a hungry hyena?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "Only for television I do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "What's that all about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "Well, I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "How does Chelsea know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "It's how I say hello.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Chelsea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "Would you mind if we do this in the studio next time, then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "Well, I was hoping you would ask me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120208pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Tell me one good reason why people should buy this book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "Because it will make you laugh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]